yaya.com 2003-06-18

# YaYa: FAQ

| 

**Privacy Policy for YaYa, LLC ("YaYa")**

Because collecting information on our registered users is an integral part of our business and in order to offer the best interactive games on the Internet, YaYa is committed to protecting the information you provide to us. This statement outlines our privacy policies and explains what information we collect from our users and why (our “Policy”).

The core of our Policy is this: YaYa will not knowingly release, sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third party without your permission, except as discussed herein or if we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect our own rights and properties. YaYa considers personal information to include, without limitation, name, e-mail address, home or billing address, phone number, user ID, passwords and credit card information (your “Personal Information”). 

We want you to feel safe and comfortable when you use our site and affiliated game sites, and we are dedicated to developing and upholding high standards for protecting your privacy and securing your Personal Information. You should read and familiarize yourself with this Policy and with the terms of use, if any, of our site and affiliated game sites. When you use our site and affiliated game sites, you agree to abide by the terms of this Policy and any relevant terms of use. We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We suggest you check this page occasionally for updates. If you have any questions, please write to us at privacy@yaya.com. 

**What Information We Collect and How We Use It:**

YaYa collects Personal Information on a voluntary basis. You do not need to provide us with information about yourself to use many areas of our site and affiliated game sites, but in order to take advantage of some of our features you may need to register and/or provide other Personal Information before you can participate. 

**We will ask you for some Personal Information:**

when you fill out the registration form for our site,   
when you register for specific promotions, and   
when you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend of our site.   
To register for our site, you will need to provide us with your name, e-mail address, zip code and date of birth. In the future, some of our features and tools may require you to provide us with additional information as well. We will use this Personal Information to contact you if necessary or, if you choose to receive e-mail from us, to send you newsletters and to inform you about special offers or events that might interest you. You always have the option to change your mind about receiving e-mail from us, to change the areas of interest about which you have requested information, or to change or update any of your Personal Information, by e-mailing us at unsubscribe@yaya.com or changes@yaya.com, respectively, and submitting the appropriate changes. 

In addition, in order to enhance your experience at our site and affiliated game sites and on the worldwide web, we keep abreast of third parties who provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. As part of our business, we have also entered into, and may in the future enter into, agreements whereby we license our games and products to companies, many of them prominent, which are seeking to enhance their presence on the worldwide web in order to benefit their customers. We may choose to provide these third parties with some or all of your Personal Information (for compensation or otherwise) in order to allow them to introduce their products and/or promotional efforts to you. Other than discussed herein, we will not knowingly sell, rent or trade any of your Personal Information. 

YaYa may also collect demographic information from users such as age, gender and areas of interest. We plan to use this information to improve our site and affiliated game sites by measuring interest, traffic and usage patterns. We may share this information with third parties, in a non-personal, aggregate form only. Advertisers pay us to place advertisements on our site and affiliated game sites and in our games, but they want to make sure that the relevant content reaches the target audience. For example, we might tell an advertiser the number of users in a certain age range that responded to an ad. This information will not identify you personally, and other than discussed herein, we will not knowingly provide any Personal Information to any third party. 

**Your Responsibility:**

Although we will protect your privacy on our site and affiliated game sites as described in this Policy, you should keep in mind that if you voluntarily disclose Personal Information online, that information may be accessible to others. This is also true if anyone else has access to your personal computer, such as an employer or family member. 

Additionally, some of our business partners, clients, and/or affiliates have web sites through which you may "opt in," by registration or otherwise, to receive information from us and/or link to our site and affiliated game sites. We make reasonable efforts to ensure, but cannot guarantee, that any Personal Information we receive from you through such an "opt-in" is covered by this Policy and protected as though such Personal Information was registered by you directly with us. 

However, if you link to a third party site from our site or affiliated game sites, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

**Referrals:**

If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend, we’ll ask you to provide the friend’s name and e-mail address. YaYa will automatically send your friend an e-mail inviting them to visit our site. YaYa stores this information for the purpose of sending this invitation e-mail. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database at any time by e-mailing changes@yaya.com. 

**Children:**

Protecting children online is of the utmost importance to YaYa. We currently define children as minors under the age of 13 years old. 

While it is not necessary to register to use most of our games, if for any reason someone under the age of 13 attempts to register with us, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian present to consent to the registration. Such consent is given by, and deemed by us to be given by, the parent registering with our site concurrently with or immediately subsequent to the child's registration. Much of the same Personal Information that would be collected from an adult is collected from a child during the registration process, if parental consent is contained. However, under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator can require, as a condition of participation in an activity, that a child under the age of 13 disclose more information than is reasonably necessary. YaYa abides by this requirement. 

We will not rent or sell children's Personal Information to any third party or client, or contact any children about special offers, if parental consent is not received at the time of the child's registration. Children and/or parents can update or delete information in the child's account by e-mailing us at changes@yaya.com and submitting the appropriate changes. 

In addition, if a parent chooses not to allow us to further collect or use the child's Personal Information, that parent can contact us to request the removal of the child's Personal Information from our database at any time by e-mailing us at changes@yaya.com. Please note that Personal Information about a child may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after a request for deletion of that child's account. This may be the case even though no information about that account remains in our active user databases. 

**Use of Cookies:**

YaYa, like most web sites, uses cookies to enhance your experience while using our site and affiliated game sites. Cookies make using our site and affiliated game sites easier by storing and tracking your preferences and passwords. Cookies are stored on your computer, and are not accessible to YaYa or any other site you may visit. 

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change your browser settings to refuse them. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site and affiliated game sites will not function properly when you view them, and you may have to enter Personal Information every time you use that site in order to participate in certain services or promotions. 

**Promotions and Prizes:**

When you register for promotions or claim prizes on our site or affiliated game sites, we may collect Personal Information and general demographic data, such as, year of birth, gender, zip code and country. Whenever we collect Personal Information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Statement on that page. 

Some of our games reward successful players with prizes that can take the form of cash or other prizes. Only certain residents of the United States and Canada (excluding Quebec) who are 18 years of age or more are eligible to receive prizes, and all prize programs are void where prohibited by law. See the “Prize Rules” for complete details. In order to award cash and other prizes, we must collect more specific Personal Information for income tax purposes. This specific Personal Information includes: full legal name, complete address (city, state, country and zip/postal code), a social security number (social insurance number in Canada) and date of birth. If this information is not collected and verified, the prize will not be awarded. 

If you win a prize, YaYa reserves the right to use your name, city and state and other information (excluding your social security number) in advertising, promotional and/or marketing materials as described in the Liability and Publicity Release on our Web-based prize claim form. 

Participation in games with a prize component is strictly voluntary and is not a required part of our service. We only request Personal Information on any relevant prize claim forms if you have voluntarily chosen to play our prize-based games. You may play prize-based games at any time, but in order to collect any prize associated with those games, you must provide the information requested. Alternatively, you may elect not to play those games or may decline any prizes awarded in those games. 

**Member Surveys:**

We occasionally run marketing surveys on our site and affiliated game sites. These surveys are used to fully understand our audience, to provide better service, as a factor in determining new features and games to add to our service, and to collect more specific aggregate demographic information. Participation in these surveys is always optional and voluntary. 

Data collected from these member surveys is used by our marketing department and occasionally shared in aggregate form with our advertisers and sponsors. We may also use survey data to direct advertising that is more likely to be of interest to you. Your Personal Information is not disclosed to a third party as part of our member surveys without your consent. 

**Security:**

YaYa has security measures in place which are designed to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information you provide us. The servers for our site and affiliated game sites are stored in a physically secure, climate-controlled facility, and all information is stored behind a barrier known as a “firewall.” The firewall is designed to prevent unauthorized individuals from accessing our servers. We also maintain internal controls in order to limit any unauthorized access to Personal Information you provide to us. 

**Changing Your E-mail Preferences:**

If you agree to receive them, YaYa may send you communications regarding products, services, promotions, changes to our site or affiliated fame sites or other information. You always have the opportunity to choose not to receive such communications by opting out of receiving communications during the registration process or by e-mailing us at unsubscribe@yaya.com. 

**Advertising:**

YaYa uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information on Doubleclick's services and how you can opt out of those services, please visit Doubleclick's website.

**Log Files:**

YaYa uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track your movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to your personally identifiable information.

YaYa may use WebSideStory's Hitbox service and cookies to measure traffic. This company specifically measures traffic to Web sites. To find out more about how WebSideStory uses the information it collects via cookies, go to http://www.websidestory.com/privacy.

**Contacting the Web Site:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site or affiliated game sites, or your dealings with our site or affiliated game sites, please feel free to contact us by sending an e-mail to [privacy@yaya.com](mailto:privacy@yaya.com). 

YaYa reserves the right to update, modify or change this Policy at any time. We suggest you check this page occasionally for updates.

|  |
